# Starrika McCloud

# **Full Stack Developer**

Cybre3@gmail.com □

(609) 815 1154

Bessemer, AL ♥

linkedin.com/in/starrika-mccloud-802a251a1

starrika-mccloud-portfolio.herokuapp.com

github.com/Cybre3

Full Stack Developer with 10 years of Entertainment Technology experience.

Troubleshooting, material digest and organizational strengths allow me to assess and resolve, hindering, daily issues. Resolutions include but not limited to: Scaling organizational networks, advising technicians in problem solving and refactoring equipment behavior programs.

Clients and fellow technicians have expressed significant increase in efficiency.

### **Achievements/Awards**

NCL: Company Excellence - "Vacation Hero" and "Outstanding Team" awards, with Norwegian Cruise Line.

Freelance: "Best Lighting Design" nomination by NJACT Perry Awards.

Non-profit: Founder of non-profit organization, "Storehouse Strength."

#### **Education**

Kingsland University – Oct. 2020 – Oct. 2021 Certified Full Stack Development

Mercer County Community College – Aug. 2011 – Dec. 2015 Entertainment Technology

Mercer County Community College – Aug. 2009 – May 2011 Electronic Engineering Technology

#### Skills

Git | GitHub HTML | CSS JavaScript PHP NoSQL MERN

MongoDB | Express | React | Node.js REST Services | Postman Jest | Mocha | Chai Netlify | Heroku

Troubleshooting
Adaptability
Organization
Detail Oriented
Teamwork
Research
Composed
Communication

### **Currently Learning**

Java Angular

## **Experience**

2013 – December 2021

Lighting Technician and Designer • Freelance • Owner MTS

- Scale organizational network by installing repeaters and extended data points for efficiency and effectiveness.
- Collaborate with directors and creative team.
- Maintain / repair equipment Update virtual Rep plots.
- Troubleshoot electrical circuits, signal connection, Lighting software and intelligent lighting fixtures.
- Design, program and keep lights for shows/events/musicals.

June 2018 – March 2020

Lighting Technician • Norwegian Cruise Lines & Holdings

- Advise and lead other technicians in troubleshooting, problem solving and programming within their venue.
- Troubleshoot electrical circuits, signal connection, lighting software and intelligent lighting fixtures.
- Design, program and keep lights for shows/events/musicals.
- Maintain / repair equipment Update virtual Rep plots.
- Create detailed/organized inventory and incoming technician handover notes.

Note: Other work experiences, not relevant to field, exist but not included.